（純一）寒い
It's really cold.
But of course, we're at the beach in winter.
（逢）当たり前じゃないですか
冬の海だから
先輩が来ようって言ったんですよ
You're the one who wanted to come here.
Yeah, but we'll probably catch a cold at this rate.
そうだけど
このままじゃ風邪ひきそうだから
あったまっていいかな？
Can I warm myself up?
Huh? Warm yourself up?
えッ　あったまるって
あッ　ちょっと先輩　何を…
Wait, Senpai! What are you...
七咲　あったか～
You're so warm, Nanasaki.
もしかして
これが目的で
You wanted to come here just to do this?
ここに来ました？
い　いいじゃないか　今日くらい
Wh-What's wrong with doing this just for today?
I mean, we haven't been seeing each other in school much.
学校では
ほとんど会えてないんだから
僕は
大学受験に向けての塾通いだし
I've been attending cram school for my university exams,
七咲は水泳部の部長とか
家事手伝いとかあるし
and you're serving as the captain of the
Swim Club along with your household chores.
そうですね
Indeed.
次の楽しみは　やっぱ
クリスマスイブのデートかな
The next thing I'm looking forward to is probably our Christmas Eve date.
はい　私も楽しみです
Yes, I'm looking forward to it too.
〈あれから　もうすぐ１年〉
It's almost been a year since then.
〈またクリスマスの季節が
近づいてきた〉
The Christmas season is approaching fast again.
〈去年は楽しかったなあ〉
Last year was a lot of fun.
〈でも　あの温泉は鹿の異常繁殖で〉
But as for that hot spring, we probably can't go up the hill since the deer have been breeding at abnormal rates.
〈山に入れなくなったみたいだし〉
We'll go somewhere else this year...
〈今年は別の場所で…〉
Senpai, about this year's Christmas Eve...
先輩　今年のクリスマスイブなんですけど
分かってる　僕は
I know... I'll...
...definitely...
絶対
...get into university...
大学に合格して
七咲に
ふさわしい男に…
...and become a man fit for you...
全く　仕方のない先輩ですね
Geez, you're such a hopeless upperclassman.
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
SS
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
（チャイム）
Coming!
（美也）は～い
あッ　おはよう　逢ちゃん
Oh! Morning, Ai-chan!
Morning, Miya-chan.
おはよう　美也ちゃん　先輩は？
Where's Senpai?
まだ寝てる　ゆうべ遅くまで
勉強してたみたいだから
He's still in bed.
Looks like he was up studying until pretty late last night, so he's still sound asleep.
グースカピーだよ
そう　分かった
お邪魔しま～す
Okay, I see.
Excuse me!
Thanks for waking him up for me, as always!
いつも代わりに起こしてくれて
ありがとうね
No problem, don't worry about it.
いいの　気にしないで
私も好きでやってるだけだから
I'm doing this because I want to.
Nii-nii's so lucky to have Ai-chan as his girlfriend.
逢ちゃんが彼女だなんて
にぃには本当に幸せ者だよね
先輩　起きてください
Senpai, wake up.
Senpai.
先輩
う　うん…
You'll be late if you don't wake up soon.
遅刻しちゃいますよ
早く起きてください
まだ眠い
I still wanna sleep.
もう時間ぎりぎりです
You don't have much time left.
学校　休むつもりですか？
Are you skipping school today?
Sounds pretty good to me...
それもいいかも…
I'll pull you out of bed if you don't get up!
起きないのであれば
布団から引っ張り出しますよ
うわッ　あッ
ちょっ　ちょっとちょっと…
W-Wait, wait!
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
（あくびをする純一）
So you were up late last night.
ゆうべも遅かったみたいですね
美也ちゃんから聞きました
Miya-chan told me.
うん　ちょっと
気合が入りすぎちゃってさ
Yeah, I got a little too into it.
受験生としての情熱が
燃え上がってきたというか
It's like my passion as a test-taker has flared up.
I know you're trying hard, but don't push yourself too much.
頑張ってるのは分かってますけど
あまり無理をしないでくださいね
うん　ありがとう
I know. Thanks.
Good morning, captain.
おはようございます　部長
おはよう
Morning.
As usual, you two are all lovey-dovey in the morning!
今日も朝からラブラブですね
なッ…
Wha...
≪（梅原）頼むよ　大将
I beg you, boss!
Wh-What's the matter, Umehara?
な　何だよ
梅原　いきなり
（梅原）このままじゃ
俺の高校３年間は灰色だ
At this rate, all three years of my
high school will be devoid of color...
何とかクリスマスまでに
彼女が欲しいんだよ
I want to get a girlfriend somehow before Christmas.
I'm sure you have connections
through your sister or girlfriend.
妹と彼女がいるお前なら
ツテくらいあるだろ
Please introduce some girl to me!
誰か女の子　紹介してくれよ～
I-I don't know if I can do that...
そ　そんなこと言われても…
お前だけが頼りなんだよ　大将
You're the only one I can count on, boss!
ちょっと落ち着けって　梅原
C-Calm down a bit, Umehara.
Come on, come on!
なあ　なあ　なあ
≪（純一・梅原）うわッ！
Keiko!
（薫）恵子　うん？
Ow...
頼むよ　なあったら　大将
I beg you, please, boss!
こんな　こんな惨めな…
This... This is too sad...
H-Hey, get off me!
何やってんの　こいつら
（恵子）さあ？
What the hell are they doing?
No clue...
≪（詞）橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
あッ　絢辻さん
Oh, Ayatsuji-san.
（詞）珍しいわね
今日は図書室で勉強？
How rare to see you here. Are
you studying at the library today?
うん　通ってる塾が休みなんで
Yeah, the cram school I go to is off today, so
I figured I'd try changing things once in a while.
たまには
気分を変えてみようと思ってね
絢辻さんも勉強？
Are you studying too?
Huh? But I thought you got an offer already...
あれッ
でも　推薦が決まったって
Yes, but it seems like studying's become a habit.
そうだけど
癖になっちゃったみたいで
勉強していないと
何となく落ち着かないの
I somehow feel uneasy when I'm not studying.
You're amazing.
すごいな　僕も癖になるくらい
勉強してくればよかった
I wish I could study until it became a habit.
それはそれで　どうなんだろう
I dunno about that.
じゃあ　またね　橘君
Well, see you later, Tachibana-kun.
うん
Yeah.
Well, this is a good place to stop, so I guess I'll go home too.
さてと　キリもいいし
僕も　そろそろ帰るか
あッ　そうだ
Oh, that's right.
（ホイッスル）
〈女子部員は　１年生も
いっぱい入って充実してるな〉
It's pretty full around here with the many freshmen girls that joined.
〈…て　違う違う〉
No, no.
〈目的を忘れるところだったな〉
I almost forgot what I came here for.
それじゃあ　次
息継ぎとキックのタイミングに注意して
Next, focus on your breathing and the timing of your kicks.
はいッ
Go!
〈すっかり部長らしくなって〉
She's become a great captain.
Just like Tsukahara-senpai was last year.
〈去年の塚原先輩みたいだ〉
えッ？
あれッ
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh"?
「あれッ」じゃありませんよ
前にも言ったけど　ここは
女子水泳部が使用している間
You should already know this, but boys aren't allowed in here when the Girls Swim Club's using the pool.
男子は立ち入り禁止です
忘れたんですか？
You forgot?
N-No, it's not that I forgot...
い　いや
忘れたわけじゃないけど
けど　何です？
Then what?
U-Uh, um...
えっと　あの…
すみません
I'm sorry.
もういいじゃないですか　部長
I think that's enough, captain.
えッ？
そうですよ
Huh?
That's right.
部長も　この時間になると　いつも
入り口の方を気にしてますし
I mean, you're always looking toward the entrance around this time.
そ　そんなこと…
Th-That's not...!
えッ？　あッ
A-Are you sorry for what you did?
は　反省してますか？
えッ？
もう二度と部活中は
ここに入らないでください
Don't come in here when club activities are going on again!
Got it?
分かりましたか？
Y-Yes, I got it!
はいッ　分かりました
もう二度と部活中は
ここに入りません　反省してます
I won't come in here when club activities are going on again.
I'll reflect on my actions.
I'm sorry!
すみませんでした
それなら…
Okay then...
No, Ai-chan!
（美也）ダメだよ　逢ちゃん
えッ？
そんなに簡単に許しちゃダメ！
You can't let him go that easily!
M-Miya! What are you doing here?!
み　美也
何でここに！？
I joined the Swim Club starting this year.
今年から
水泳部に入部したんだも～ん
き　聞いてないぞ
I-I had no idea!
教えてないよ
I never told you.
何で　そんなこと
Why would you do that?
Isn't it more fun to keep it secret?
秘密にしといた方が面白いじゃん
今回みたいにさ
Just like this time.
I'm sure you knew about it, Nanasaki.
七咲は知ってたんだよな　当然
Miya-chan told me to keep quiet about it-
黙っててって頼まれたもので
More importantly, you can't let him go that easily, Ai-chan!
そんなことより
そんなに簡単に許しちゃダメだよ
逢ちゃんだけじゃなくて
Onii-chan wasn't just looking at you. He was also looking at the other girls in their swimsuits and smirking, you know.
他の子の水着も見て
ニヤニヤしてたんだから
えッ？
I-I wasn't smirking!
ニヤニヤなんかしてない
You're full of lies.
嘘ばっかり
嘘じゃない
I'm not lying.
Why do you have such a pervy look on your face, then?
じゃあ
どうして鼻の下が伸びてるの？
I-I don't...!
伸びてなんか…
You fell for it, Onii-chan!
引っかかったね　お兄ちゃん
先輩
Senpai.
ち　違う　誤解だ
N-No, it's all a misunderstanding!
W-Wait, listen to me!
待って　話を聞いて
うわあ～ッ！
全く　信じられません
You're seriously unbelievable!
すみません
I'm sorry.
本当に先輩はエッチなんですね
You're seriously such a perv, Senpai.
知ってましたけど
Though I already knew that.
でも　僕は本当に七咲に
会うためにプールに行ったんだ
But I really did go to the pool just to meet you.
今日は塾が休みだから
久々に一緒に帰れるかなと思って
I don't have cram school today and I figured we could go home together since it's been so long...
So... um...
だから　その…
分かりました　許してあげます
I see. I forgive you.
Nanasaki...
七咲
その代わり
In return...
あッ　はいッ
R-Right!
罰として
お買い物に付き合ってください
...come with me on my grocery shopping as punishment.
えッ？
今日は近くのスーパーで
They're doing a huge discount for
up to two packs of eggs per person
お一人様２パックまでの卵と
お一人様１本までの牛乳が
大特価なんです
and one bottle of milk per person at the nearby supermarket.
そういう罰なら喜んで付き合うよ
I'll gladly take the punishment of going with you!
だからって　今度のぞいたら
Just saying, I really won't forgive you if you dare to peek again!
本当に許しませんよ
はい
Okay.
I n f i r m a r y
七咲…
Nanasaki?
Sorry, did I wake you?
すみません　起こしちゃいましたか
いや　いいよ
Nah, it's fine.
布団
直してくれたんだ　ありがとう
You fixed the sheets for me.
Thanks.
Ah, you don't have to get up. Keep laying down.
あッ　いいですよ
そのまま寝ててください
でも　どうして七咲がここに？
But what are you doing here, Nanasaki?
先輩を捜してたんです
I was looking for you.
一緒に
お昼ご飯でも　どうかなと
I was wondering if we could have lunch together.
あッ　ごめん
気にしないでください
Ah, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I heard from Miya-chan that you were up late studying last night.
ゆうべも勉強してたこと
美也ちゃんに聞きましたから
Yeah.
うん　あッ
どうしました？
What's wrong?
いや　美也って聞いて思い出してさ
You reminded me of something when you mentioned Miya.
そういえば　あいつ
よく小さい頃
She often used to sleep on my
dad's belly when she was small.
父さんのおなかを
枕にして寝てたなって
そうですか　うちの郁夫は
I see.
My brother Ikuo falls asleep right
away when you sing him a lullaby.
子守歌を歌ってあげると
すぐに寝つきますよ
おなかを枕にはしませんけど
He doesn't sleep on my belly, though.
ハハッ　そうなんだ
I see.
Yep.
はい
ふ～ん
先輩？
Senpai?
あのさ
はい
You know...
Yes?
今　思ったんだけど　その…
I was just thinking... well...
七咲のおなかを枕にして
子守歌を歌ってもらえたら
If I could sleep on your belly while you sing me a lullaby...
I'd probably sleep very well.
すごく　よく眠れるんじゃないかな
What? Here?!
えッ　ここでですか？
できれば
If you don't mind...
N-No way!
嫌です　誰かに見られたら
恥ずかしいじゃないですか
It'll be really embarrassing if someone saw us!
It's fine, we could just pull the curtains around the bed...
大丈夫　ベッドの周りには
カーテンがあるし　それを閉めれば
I'm sure it'll blow away my fatigue from the studying.
きっと勉強の疲れも
ぶっ飛んじゃうと思うんだよね
ダメ…　かな？
You don't want to?
分かりました
Fine, then.
それで　どうすればいいんですか？
So... how do we do this?
Um...
あの　何で目を塞いでるの？
Why are you covering my eyes?
だって　恥ずかしいじゃないですか
This is pretty embarrassing, you know.
う　動かないでください
D-Don't move!
あッ　ごめん
Sorry.
じゃあ　いきます
Well, here I go.
お願いします
Please.
にゃ～ん　にゃ～ん
ごろ～り～よ
Meow, meow~
Lay down~
にゃんご～ろ～り～
Meow, lay down~
坊や～は～良い子～だ
You're a good boy~
ねんね～しな～
It's time for bed~
にゃん子～の　おも～り～は
Your sleepiness will go away~
どこ～へ～行った～
先輩？
Senpai?
ホント　すごくよく眠ってる
He really is sleeping very well.
郁夫　宿題が終わったら
明日の準備して　早く寝なさ…
Ikuo!
When you're done with your homework,
get ready for tomorrow and sleep early...
Come on, get up, Ikuo.
ほら　起きて　郁夫
You'll catch a cold if you sleep in the kotatsu.
こたつで寝たら　風邪ひいちゃうよ
（郁夫）うう…
あッ　そうだ
Oh, that's right!
クリスマスイブに　どこへ行くか
I'll need to decide with Senpai
where to go for Christmas Eve soon!
早く先輩と決めておかなくちゃ
えッ？
What?
I'm really sorry!
ホントごめん！
いや　あの
Well, uh...
いきなり謝られても
何のことだかサッパリ
I have no idea what you're apologizing for if you just do it suddenly...
Yesterday, I got the results for the mock exams I had in cram school a week ago.
実は昨日　塾で１週間前にやった
模試の結果が返ってきてさ
はあ
And, well... how should I say this...
それが　その何ていうか…
悪かった？
It was bad?
Yeah.
どれぐらい？
How bad?
塾の中でも
下から数えた方が早いくらい
You'd reach me quicker if you started counting from the bottom of my class.
えッ？
い　いや
N-No!
I got most of the questions right. Really.
答えは　ほとんど合ってたんだよ
It's just that... all my answers were off by one row on the answer sheet...
ただ
解答欄が１個ずつズレてただけで
分かりやすいミスですね
面目ない
That's an understandable mistake.
How embarrassing...
But you didn't need to apologize for that.
でも　それくらいなら
謝ることないですよ
Just do it right next time.
次から　ちゃんとすれば
いや
Well, that isn't actually what I'm apologizing for...
実は謝ってるのは
そのことじゃなくてさ
Hmm? Then what?
うん？
じゃあ　何を
うちの塾
すごいスパルタ式なんだよ
My cram school's really tough.
それで
模試の結果が悪かった人は全員
Everyone who did badly in the mocks has to go to this training camp that will take place soon.
近いうちに行われる
合宿に行かなくちゃならなくて
And it starts on December 23rd.
それが始まるのが
１２月２３日からなんだ
えッ？
もちろん塾の先生には言ったよ
I did talk to the cram school teacher!
「解答欄がズレてただけだし」
I told him I shouldn't need to go since my answers would be right if they weren't off by one row.
「答えが合ってるから
いいじゃないですか」って
But he said it's not like I can make this excuse if I made the same mistake in the real thing.
そしたら
「本番で同じミスをしても」
「そうやって
言い訳するのか」と言われて
Rumor has it that they have this really scary camp leader there.
噂では　すごい怖い寮長のいる所に
放り込まれるらしいんだ
しかも　ほぼ監禁状態で
What's worse, we're pretty much confined inside
朝の５時に起床してから
夜寝るまで　自由時間もなく
and have to wake up at five in the morning and study without any free time all the way until bedtime...
ひたすら勉強させられるって
《オッホッホッホ》
《オーッホッホッホ…》
I... see.
そう…　ですか
うん　あのさ
Yeah.
Hey...
気にしないでください
Don't worry about it.
えッ？
実は　私も創設祭の後に
I actually also have to go to the after party for the
Girls Swim Club's Oden stall after the Founder's Festival.
女子水泳部でやる　おでん屋台の
打ち上げに出ることになっていて
I was worried that it would cut into our date.
デートの時間がとれるか　不安で
えッ　そうなの？
はい
Really?
Yes.
ほら　私　部長ですから
出ないわけにもいかなくて
I mean, I'm the team captain, so I have to go.
だから　ちょうどいいっていうか
I guess it's convenient that it happened...
なので　気にしないでください
So please don't worry about it.
Ah, okay.
あッ　うん
H-Hey...
あのさ
I'll definitely make up for this, so...
この埋め合わせは
必ず　するから
はい　楽しみにしてます
Yes, I'll be looking forward to it.
先輩は合宿
頑張ってきてくださいね
Please work hard in the training camp!
Yeah, I will!
うんッ　頑張るよ
≪（紗江）あの　今年の創設祭で→
Um, our class has decided to do a
play in this year's Founder's Festival...
うちのクラスは
劇をやることに決まって→
その配役とか　裏方の人とか
So I'd like us to decide on the cast and backstage roles...
Founder's Festival
Play
Roles
役割分担を決めたいと思います
何か意見のある人は
手を挙げてください
Please raise your hand if you have any opinions.
〈何で
あんなこと言っちゃったんだろ〉
Why did I say something like that?
The morning training for the swim meet that'll take place early next year will start next week.
〈年明けの大会に向けて〉
〈来週から朝練も始まるし〉
〈創設祭の準備もあるから〉
There's also the Founder's Festival preparations, which means we'll be able to meet each other even less...
〈ますます会えなくなるのに〉
Hey, what role do you want, Ai-chan?
ねえねえ　逢ちゃんは何の役やる？
おでん屋台もあるけど
こっちも出たいよね
I know you have the Oden stall, but I want you to do this too!
どうせなら両方楽しく
みたいにさ
You might as well enjoy both while you're at it!
逢ちゃん？
Ai-chan?
Ode
Sure
Pass
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
どうかな？
How's this?
ヒヒーン　馬だぞ
It's a horse!
〈もうすぐ
先輩が合宿に行っちゃう〉
Senpai will be going to the training camp soon.
〈膝掛けくらいしか
用意できなかったけど〉
I couldn't prepare anything other than a lap blanket for him...
But it should be okay, right? He can use it in the training camp...
〈いいよね
合宿で使ってもらえるし〉
〈少し早いけど
先輩を応援するための〉
It's a little early, but my Christmas present to him will show that I'm rooting for him.
〈私からのクリスマスプレゼント〉
What do you think are some good places to go to on a Christmas date, Kaoru?
（恵子）クリスマスデートの行き先だけど
どこに行ったらいいと思う？
≪（薫）クリスマスデート？
A Christmas date?
Let's see...
そうね　やっぱド定番は
ポートタワーとかじゃない？
The Port Tower is a popular choice.
だね
あとは遊園地とか
Yeah!
Then there's also the amusement park, the cinema and the karaoke bar!
映画館とか　カラオケとか！
映画でクリスマスデートに合うようなやつ
やってたかな
I wonder if they'll have movies suitable for a Christmas date at the cinema.
さあ？　あッ
I dunno...
That reminds me, I hear they're doing a special lightup at the aquarium just for Christmas.
そういえば　水族館で
クリスマス限定のライトアップやるって
うわ～　素敵
That's wonderful!
幻想的な夜の水族館で
A Christmas Eve spent together with the
one you love at the magical aquarium at night...
大好きな人と過ごす
二人っきりのクリスマスイブ→
ロマンチック～
How romantic!
Influenced by such an atmosphere, any guy would fall to his knees!
（薫）雰囲気にあてられて
どんな男もイチコロよね
Just thinking about it is making my heart race!
想像するだけでドキドキしちゃう
Wait, there's no point in this if you
don't get a boyfriend in the first place.
まずは
彼氏つくらないと意味ないでしょ
Hehe, you're right.
テヘッ　そうだね
≪（美也）大変だよ　逢ちゃん！
This is bad, Ai-chan!
何が？
What?
Onii-chan was taken to the cram school training camp last night!
お兄ちゃん　昨日の夜
塾の合宿に連れていかれた
What? But I thought he was scheduled to go later...
えッ
予定では　まだ先…
それがね　特に成績の悪かった人は
Well, the people with especially bad grades have to start earlier and therefore do it for longer.
早くから始めて
長くやるんだって→
The cram school people suddenly
showed up and took Onii-chan away!
いきなり塾の人達が来て→
お兄ちゃん　連れていっちゃった
《美也　このことを》
Miya!
Make sure you tell Nanasaki!
《七咲に伝えて！》
そう…　そうなんだ
I... I see.
Yeah.
うんッ　逢ちゃん？
Ai-chan?
〈先輩〉
Senpai...
〈今頃　ちゃんと勉強してるかな〉
I wonder if he's studying hard right now?
〈先輩も頑張ってるんだから〉
Senpai's working hard, so I have to endure this, too...
〈私も我慢しないと〉
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
ボクに時の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへもいけない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
キミに渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来にちりばめた予定は隣に キミがいて欲しい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度も溜息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただ一つだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
「好きだよ」
Suki da yo
"I love you"
ボクの告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
先輩
七咲
Senpai.
Nanasaki.
先輩　私…
分かってる
Senpai, I...
I know.
クリスマスイブに
一人にしてごめん
Sorry for leaving you alone on Christmas Eve.
I...
私　一人でも　たくましく
生きていくので
Nanasaki.
I may be alone, but I'll live on bravely, so
please watch over me from the distant heavens.
遠い空の上から私を
見守っていてください
Hey, wait!
待って！
僕　生きてるから
I'm still alive!
塾の合宿に
強制参加させられただけ
I was just forced to attend the cram school training camp!
Just kidding.
冗談です
全く
Geez, don't surprise me like that.
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
ビックリさせないでよ
Next episode: "Escape".
〈でも　やっぱり寂しい〉
But I do feel lonely, after all...